In today's video, I'm gonna be talking about YC and why it is the best startup accelerator in 2025.
YC has been around since 2005, setting the bar high for launching startups.
They have backed startups like Airbnb, Reddit, OpenAI, yeahhh, those.
So what makes YC special?
1. Mentorship from real founders.
2. The $500,000 upfront
3. The networking. Thousands of founders trying to help each other.
I first discovered YC in 2022, and since that day, my perception about building startups has completely changed.
Now, I'm even applying with my own startup, Wands. It's an AI-powered video editing agent, which means that can edit the video for you. You send the video, it's gonna be edited in like one, two minutes, no more.
If you're building something like me, check out ycombinator.com. See you in SF.